[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Diamond formation is a very slow process. It is estimated that most diamonds found in nature are of what approximate age?", "correct_answer": "1 \u2013 3 billion years old", "incorrect_answers": ["100 \u2013 200 million years old", "30 \u2013 40 billion years old", "100 000 \u2013 200 000 years old"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Japanese ship, involved in S.P.E.C.T.R.E.s evil scheme in the James Bond You Only Live Twice?", "correct_answer": "Ning-Po", "incorrect_answers": ["Mu-San", "Feng-Li", "Kong-Wu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Human toes and  fingers go by what common name?", "correct_answer": "Phalanges", "incorrect_answers": ["Tarsals", "Carpals", "Vertabrae"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who invented a process to remove caffeine from coffee for the first time?", "correct_answer": "Roselius and Wimmer", "incorrect_answers": ["Rostand and Martin", "Banting and Best", "Nestle and Sanders"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie Valley Girl, where are Julie and Randy headed in the limo?", "correct_answer": "Valley Sheridan", "incorrect_answers": ["Valley Ramada", "Valley Best Western", "Valley Holiday Inn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Boiling broccoli for more than ten minutes reduces its beneficial properties. Which of these cooking methods is more appropriate for preserving its ingredients?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Stir-frying", "Steaming", "Microwaving"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Electrooculography is a medical procedure which inspects the potential of which bodily organ?", "correct_answer": "Retina", "incorrect_answers": ["Inner ear", "Adrenal glands", "Taste buds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During a scene of the movie Red Dawn, the Wolverines come across a downed American Air Force pilot. What type of aircraft does he say he flies?", "correct_answer": "F-15", "incorrect_answers": ["F-16", "Stealth", "F-14"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these was not among the directors of The Longest Day?", "correct_answer": "James Jones", "incorrect_answers": ["Ken  Annakin", "Bernhard  Wicki", "Andrew  Marton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the anatomical differences between African elephants and Asian elephants?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["In the tusks", "In the ears", "In the body size"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first Sign of the Chinese Zodiac.  It is a Yang Sign commonly associated with the Water Element.", "correct_answer": "Rat", "incorrect_answers": ["Dog", "Horse", "Pig"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This soul singer and songwriter, often called Silky Smooth because of his rich baritone, is famous for his hits Rainy Night in Georgia, Fools Rush In, This Time of the Year.", "correct_answer": "Brook Benton", "incorrect_answers": ["Jackie Wilson", "David Ruffin", "Sam Cook"]}]